taking a peek into the world of graphic
让我们一窥图形世界
design for the first time can be a bit
第一次设计可能会有一点
overwhelming
压倒性
there's a lot to learn in terms of
在以下方面有很多需要学习的地方
design principles color theory
设计原则色彩理论
techniques and branding in general but
技术和品牌一般，但
if you want to create digital art then
如果你想创作数字艺术，那么
you first have to familiarize yourself
你首先得熟悉一下自己
with the tools that we use as graphic
使用我们作为图形使用的工具
designers
设计师
as of right now the industry standard is
到目前为止，行业标准是
the adobe creative suite with
土坯创意套房，配有
applications like photoshop and
应用程序如Photoshop和
illustrator leading the way
Illustrator带头
these programs cost a lot of money
这些项目花费了很多钱
though and they come with some pretty
不过，它们还附带了一些漂亮的
daunting hardware requirements
令人生畏的硬件要求
this can be a bit off-putting for
这可能会让人有点不舒服
someone who just has a casual passing
一个只是偶然路过的人
interest in graphic design
对平面设计感兴趣
and because of this you may find
正因为如此，你可能会发现
yourself looking into free alternatives
你自己在寻找免费的替代品
like inkscape and
像Inkscape和
and wondering what the differences are
想知道有什么不同
in this video i'll be comparing both
在这段视频中，我将比较这两个
applications going over what their
应用程序检查他们的
intended uses are
预期用途为
the pros and cons of each and most
每一个和最大的
importantly i'll be helping you
重要的是我会帮你
determine which one is best for you
确定哪一种最适合你
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this video we'll be doing a
这段视频我们将制作一段
comprehensive comparison
综合比较
of both inkscape and the first
Inkscape和First
thing you need to understand about
你需要了解的一件事
inkscape and is that
Inkscape和那是
although they're both free and open
尽管它们都是免费和开放的
source design applications
源代码设计应用程序
they're actually quite different
它们实际上完全不同
comparing inkscape versus is no way
比较Inkscape和Inkscape是不可能的
an apples to apples comparison
苹果与苹果的比较
they're two very different tools with
它们是两种截然不同的工具
very different intentions
非常不同的意图
let's have a closer look
让我们仔细看看
despite the various different types of
尽管有各种不同类型的
graphic formats that exist in the world
世界上存在的图形格式
the types we'll be looking at in this
我们将在本文中看到的类型
video are raster and vector and it's
视频是栅格和矢量，它的
important to understand the differences
了解不同之处很重要
between these two because they both
在这两者之间，因为他们都
represent the intended uses
代表预期用途
for inkscape and rasterization is a
对于Inkscape和光栅化是一个
digital imagery format where the image
数字图像格式，其中图像
is made of individual colored boxes
是由单独的彩色盒子组成的
known as pixels
称为像素
and it's the format that you're probably
它的格式很可能就是
most familiar with this is commonly used
最熟悉这一点的常用
in things like photos
在照片之类的东西上
jpegs and other types of imagery you
Jpeg和其他类型的图像
commonly see on the web
在网上经常看到
the raster format is preferred if you're
如果满足以下条件，则首选栅格格式
going to do any kind of design work
去做任何类型的设计工作
where you'll be editing photographs but
你将在那里编辑照片，但
it's not ideal for things like
对于像这样的事情来说，它不是很理想
illustrations and
插图和
designs where you need clean lines and
您需要清晰的线条和
crisp edges
清脆的边缘
vector graphics on the other hand are a
另一方面，矢量图形是一种
different type of imagery format
不同类型的图像格式
altogether
总而言之
vector graphics are not made of pixels
矢量图形不是由像素组成的
they're a series of coordinate points
它们是一系列的坐标点
that dictate the properties of a graphic
它规定了图形的属性
on an x and y
在x和y上
axis this makes vector graphics ideal
轴：这使矢量图形成为理想之选
for things like illustrations
对于插图之类的东西
and designs where you need to have crisp
和设计，你需要有清爽的
definitive edges
确定的边
but it's not the ideal format for
但这不是最理想的格式
working with photos where inkscape and
使用Inkscape和
come into play is that is
发挥作用的是，那就是
intended for working with raster imagery
适用于处理栅格图像
making it ideal for editing photos and
使其成为编辑照片和
inkscape
墨迹
is a vector graphics editor making it
是一个矢量图形编辑器制作它
ideal for creating digital illustrations
创建数字插图的理想选择
let's take a more in-depth look at this
让我们更深入地了解一下
is a free and open source
是一个免费的开源软件
application that functions in the raster
在栅格中运行的应用程序
environment
环境
and it's widely recognized as the go-to
它被广泛认为是
free alternative for adobe photoshop
Adobe Photoshop的免费替代品
which stands for general image
它代表一般的形象
manipulation program
操纵程序
was originally founded in 1995 by
最初成立于1995年，由
developers spencer kimball and peter
开发商斯宾塞·金博尔和彼得
mattis who were both students at uc
马蒂斯，他们都是加州大学的学生
berkeley at the time
当时的伯克利
according to wikipedia it was a
根据维基百科的说法，这是一个
semester-long project they were working
他们正在做的长达一学期的项目
on for the experimental computing
关于实验计算的讨论
facility
设施
as the years went by continued to
随着岁月的流逝，
evolve as it saw lots of
进化因为它看到了许多
updates and new features from a bustling
更新和新功能来自繁忙的
community of users and supporters
用户和支持者社区
believe it or not was actually used
信不信由你，它实际上被用来
to create the original google logo in
要在中创建原始的Google徽标
so keep that in mind for the next time
所以下次一定要记住这一点
that somebody wants to tell you that
有人想告诉你
professional work can't be done with
专业的工作是不能用
open source software
开源软件
would be the ideal program for you
会是你理想的项目
if you're a photographer looking to
如果你是一名摄影师，希望
retouch your photos
修改你的照片
it allows you to adjust things like the
它允许您调整诸如
white balance the exposure
白平衡曝光
color saturation and it allows for some
色彩饱和度，它允许一些
complex color correction using curves
利用曲线进行复杂的颜色校正
and levels as well
和水平也一样
it even has some cool features that
它甚至有一些很酷的功能，
allow you to do things like alter the
允许您执行一些操作，如更改
shadows and highlights of a photograph
照片的阴影和高光
as well as the brightness and contrast
以及亮度和对比度
would also be ideal if you're just
也是理想的，如果你只是
looking to crop an image or maybe crop
希望裁剪图像或裁剪
something from an image and remove
从图像中删除某些内容
the background there's some really
背景是有一些真正的
advanced tools and features that allow
先进的工具和功能，允许
you to extract subjects from your photos
你需要从你的照片中提取主题
even if they have strands of hair and
即使他们有一缕头发和
other fine details that make it
其他细节使它成为
difficult to define
难以定义
you can also use to make some quick
你也可以用来快速制作一些
and easy corrections to subtle
以及对微妙的简单修正
imperfections like
不完美的地方，比如
skin blemishes and yellow teeth you can
皮肤瑕疵和黄牙
change the color of someone's eyes
改变某人眼睛的颜色
create different color variations for a
创建不同的颜色变化
product that you may be selling
您可能正在销售的产品
and you can even restore color to black
你甚至可以将颜色恢复为黑色
and white photos and by the way i have
和白色照片，顺便说一句，我有
lessons demonstrating how to do all of
演示如何执行所有操作的课程
these things on my channel
我频道上的这些东西
if you want to check that out isn't
如果你想查清楚那不是
just used for editing photos though
只是用来编辑照片的
you can also use it to create some
您还可以使用它来创建一些
pretty cool effects to interact with
与之互动的效果相当酷
your photos like
你的照片就像
a sliced effect mosaic collages 3d
一种切片效果的马赛克拼贴3D
text and you could even turn yourself
短信，你甚至可以把你自己
into a caricature if you'd like
变成漫画，如果你愿意的话
finally is the right tool for you
最终是适合您的工具
if you do a lot of sketching
如果你画了很多素描
painting or airbrushing it comes
不管是粉刷还是喷漆都会来的
equipped with lots of
配备了大量的
brushes and presets attended for
刷子和预置用于
freehand drawing whether it be by mouse
无论是用鼠标写意，还是用鼠标
or with a drawing tablet
或者用绘图板
you can even download brushes that were
你甚至可以下载画笔
intended for photoshop and use them in
适用于Photoshop，并在
and if you can't find the brush you're
如果你找不到画笔，你就是
looking for you can simply create a
寻找你可以简单地创建一个
custom brush of your own
您自己定制的画笔
although is a great tool it's not
虽然是一个很棒的工具，但它不是
the right tool for everything
万物皆宜的工具
a good example of this would be for
这方面的一个很好的例子是
designing things like logos
设计像标志这样的东西
symbols and other types of simple iconic
符号和其他类型的简单图标
illustrations
插图
these things have lots of individual
这些东西有很多个性
moving parts that you need to regularly
定期移动您需要的部件
move around and transform
四处走动，转型
independent of the rest of the image and
独立于图像的其余部分，并且
the way that functions just
它的运作方式只是
isn't suitable for this sort of thing it
它不适合做这种事情
can technically be done
从技术上讲可以做到
but it's kind of like using a fork to
但这有点像用叉子
eat your cereal you're making life a
吃你的麦片吧，你让生活变得
little more difficult for yourself than
对你自己来说比
it needs to be because
它需要是因为
there's better tools that you can use
有更好的工具可以使用
another problem with using is that
使用的另一个问题是
by nature
天性使然
the designs you create will not be
您创建的设计将不会
scalable you can scale
可扩展，您可以扩展
down without a problem but if you try to
没有问题，但如果你试着
enlarge your image you're going to end
放大你的形象，你将结束
up with pixelation
使用像素化
or in other words the individual colored
或者换句话说，个体有色人种
boxes that make up the image
构成图像的方框
are going to become more visible this
将会变得更加明显
reduces the quality and resolution of
降低图像的质量和分辨率
the image
形象
if you want a more dynamic graphic that
如果您需要更动态的图形，
can be scaled to fit
可以根据需要进行调整
many different sizes and applications
许多不同的大小和应用
then it's best to stick with vectors
那么最好坚持使用向量
let's talk a little bit about inkscape
让我们来谈谈Inkscape
now unlike
现在不同于
inkscape doesn't work with pixels it's a
Inkscape不适用于像素，它是一个
vector graphics editor and it's widely
矢量图形编辑和它的广泛应用
recognized as the best free alternative
公认为最好的免费替代品
to adobe illustrator
以土坯为插图画家
inkscape started out as a code fork for
Inkscape一开始是一个代码分支，用于
sodipode an open source vector graphics
Sodipode开源矢量图形
editor that was discontinued in 2004.
2004年停产的编辑。
the project was led by developers ted
该项目由开发人员泰德领导
gould bryce harrington
古尔德·布莱斯·哈林顿
nathan hearst and another developer who
内森·赫斯特和另一位开发人员
goes by the name mental guy
他的名字叫精神病人
inkscape has come a long way since then
从那时起，Inkscape已经走过了很长一段路
they've added lots of useful features
他们增加了很多有用的功能
like
喜欢
live path effects text manipulation and
实时路径效果文本处理和
various third-party extensions
各种第三方扩展
the core functionality of inkscape
Inkscape的核心功能
remains the same though so you never
保持不变，所以你永远不会
quite feel like you have to relearn
我觉得你必须重新学习
anything
什么都行
despite all of the additions and
尽管有了所有的补充和
improvements
改进
inkscape would be the best tool to use
Inkscape将是最好的使用工具
for designing logos
用于设计徽标
logo design is unique from other types
标志设计是有别于其他类型的
of design because logos are typically
因为徽标通常是
used in a wider variety of contexts
在更广泛的上下文中使用
a logo needs to be scaled up large
徽标需要放大
enough to work as a sign
足以作为一种标志
and resize to fit various different
并调整大小以适应各种不同的
dimensions
维数
one of the benefits of working with
使用的好处之一是
vector graphics is that they can be
矢量图形是它们可以
scaled up
纵向扩展
infinitely without quality loss this
无限无质量损失这
means that you can take your logo and
意味着你可以拿着你的徽标
enlarge it for use on a billboard or the
将其放大以用于广告牌或
side of a van
货车的侧面
without having to worry about pixelation
而不必担心像素化
the vector format is the best
矢量格式是最好的
platform for providing a logo with the
用于提供徽标的平台
versatility that it needs
其所需的多功能性
inkscape is also useful when it comes to
Inkscape在以下方面也很有用
creating simple illustrations like icons
创建简单的插图，如图标
buttons and user interface inkscape
按钮和用户界面Inkscape
makes it easy to work with simple shapes
使您可以轻松处理简单的形状
and objects that can be combined and
以及可以组合在一起的对象和
transformed into whatever you like
变成了你喜欢的任何东西
you can also adjust the coordinate
您还可以调整坐标
points of an object otherwise known as
物体的点，也称为
nodes
节点
to create your custom shapes another
要创建自定义形状，请使用另一个
thing inkscape is great for is creating
Inkscape的伟大之处在于创造
digital illustrations
数码插图
mascots and characters with a
吉祥物和带有
cartoon-like style
卡通风格
this can technically be done with
从技术上讲，这可以通过
as well but the vector format allows you
也一样，但是矢量格式允许您
to give your illustrations clean
把你的插图做得干干净净
crisp and definitive lines making
清晰明确的线条制作
inkscape the ideal tool for this
Inkscape是实现这一目标的理想工具
and if you're creating characters for a
如果你正在为一个
2d game design then you're going to need
2D游戏设计，那么你将需要
the scalable benefit
可扩展的优势
of working with vectors as well inkscape
使用向量以及Inkscape
would also be the best tool for
也是最好的工具
designing graphics for mobile
为移动设备设计图形
applications like
应用程序如
app icons splash screens buttons and
应用程序图标闪屏按钮和
various other types of user interface
各种其他类型的用户界面
the vector format is great for this
矢量格式非常适合这一点
because it provides the versatility
因为它提供了多功能性
needed for these designs to fit
需要这些设计来适应
any screen resolution without quality
任何没有质量的屏幕分辨率
loss
损失
finally the illustrative nature of
最后是说明性的
inkscape allows you to create some other
Inkscape允许您创建一些其他
unique types of designs like
独特的设计类型，如
infographics charts and repeatable
信息图表和可重复使用的图表
background tiles with an abstract
带有摘要的背景瓷砖
pattern
图案
one of the downsides of inkscape is that
Inkscape的缺点之一是
you can only work with photos in a very
您只能在非常小的空间中处理照片
limited capacity
容量有限
since inkscape is intended for creating
由于Inkscape旨在创建
vector designs
向量设计
there's really not much you can do with
你真的无能为力
rasterized photographs
栅格化照片
you can create clipping paths to remove
您可以创建要移除的剪切路径
the background or
背景或
even use them as a texture mask if you
甚至将它们用作纹理蒙版，如果您
like but that's about it
就像，但仅此而已
if you're looking to do any kind of
如果你想做任何形式的
extensive photo editing
广泛的照片编辑
you're better off sticking with
你最好还是坚持下去
another downside to using inkscape is
使用Inkscape的另一个缺点是
that it's not ideal for doing any kind
它不适合做任何一种
of painting or sketching
指绘画或素描
there are tools that allow you to paint
有一些工具可以让你画画
and sketch in inkscape but they should
并用Inkscape写生，但他们应该
only be used in a limited capacity
只能在有限的容量中使用
the way that vector graphics works is
矢量图形的工作方式是
that you'll put a lot of strain on your
你会给你的工作带来很大压力
hardware
硬件
if you create too many brush strokes and
如果您创建了太多的画笔笔划和
the file size will be enormous
文件大小将是巨大的
not only that but you won't get all of
不仅如此，你也不会得到所有
the brush settings and realistic
笔刷设置和逼真
textures that you get
您获得的纹理
with something like
像这样的东西
the application that you should use when
在以下情况下应使用的应用程序
choosing between inkscape and
在Inkscape和Inkscape之间选择
depends entirely on the type of design
完全取决于设计的类型
work you're doing
你正在做的工作
if you're working with a lot of photos
如果你正在处理大量的照片
you should probably stick to
你可能应该坚持
but if you're creating simple
但如果您要创建简单的
illustrations then you're better off
插图，那你就更好了
with inkscape
使用Inkscape
one software is not objectively better
一款软件客观上并不更好
than the other it depends entirely on
而不是它完全依赖的另一个
the context of what you're designing
您正在设计的内容的上下文
if you're wondering if it's more
如果你想知道是不是更多
important to learn one over the other
学一学比学另一种重要
it's not they're both equally important
这并不是说它们都同样重要
as a graphic designer you should
作为一名平面设计师，你应该
familiarize yourself with both
熟悉这两种语言
vector and raster design knowing how to
知道如何进行矢量和栅格设计
work with both allows you to create some
使用这两种方法可以创建一些
really dynamic designs combining
真正动感的设计组合
elements from both inkscape
来自两种水墨景观的元素
and and it'll make you a more
它会让你变得更加
complete designer as well
也是完整的设计师
if you'd like to learn more about
如果您想了解更多信息
inkscape and i have hundreds of
inkscape和我有数百个
tutorials on this channel that will walk
该频道上的教程将行走
you through each step in such a way that
您以这样的方式完成每一步，
even a first-time user could follow
即使是第一次使用的用户也可以关注
along
沿着
i also have video courses for each
我还为每个人提供视频课程
application where i go through every
我经历了每一个应用程序
tool and feature and explain how it all
工具和功能并解释这一切
works
作品
and that should do it for today's video
今天的视频就可以了
if you have any questions for which
如果您有任何疑问
software you should use for a particular
您应该用于特定的软件
type of design that i may not have
我可能没有的设计类型
covered in this video
本视频涵盖
just leave a comment below and as always
只需在下面留下评论，一如既往
thanks for watching
感谢收看
you
你